flashfxp.com 2013-06-22

# FlashFXP Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

**•** To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

**•** To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**•** To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

**•** To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

**•** To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and product updates pertaining to your order or request.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can opt-out by changing your customer settings via the customer portal.

**How do we protect your information?**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (i.e. credit card number) will not be stored on our servers.

**Private Information Security**   
For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway providers, PayPal, Avangate, and share-it! keep this information encrypted and secure on your behalf. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Third Party Disclosure**   
Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the customer portal and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**   
We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on **August 3, 2012**

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

OpenSight Software, LLC  
5309 Oak Street, PMB #215  
Quincy, Illinois 62305  
United States

**Privacy Policy Customer Pledge**   
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commision Fair  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the [Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form](http://secure.trust-guard.com/DisputeResolution/). 

Respectfully,   
OpenSight Software, LLC  
Charles DeWeese CEO  
`flashfxp.com`

flashfxp.com's privacy policy has been verified by [Trust Guard](http://www.trust-guard.com/)
